kadencethemes.com 2018-09-02

# Privacy Policy - Kadence Themes

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.kadencethemes.com (the “website”).

#### Who we are

KadenceThemes is business based in the United States of America. Our website address www.kadencethemes.com.

#### General Information

Customer information is collected for the purpose of processing orders, maintain customer accounts, maintaining customer support through email and our support forums and maintaining customer relationships through email. A customer may unsubscribe to all forms of communication or request their account be removed at any time by sending an email with their request to [info@kadencethemes.com](mailto:info@kadencethemes.com).

#### What we collect and store

 **While you visit our site, we’ll track:**

Products you’ve viewed: we’ll use this to, for example, show you products you’ve recently viewed  
Location, IP address and browser type: we’ll use this for purposes like estimating taxes and shipping as well as tracking trends  
We’ll also use cookies to keep track of cart contents while you’re browsing our site. You can read more about the cookies we use in the cookies section.

###### When/if you purchase from us

When/if you purchase from us, we’ll ask you to provide information including your name, billing address, email address, credit card/payment details and account information like a password. We’ll use this information for purposes, such as, to:

Send you information about your account and order and product information  
Respond to your requests, including refunds and complaints  
Process payments and prevent fraud  
Set up your account for our store  
Comply with any legal obligations we have, such as calculating taxes  
Improve our store offerings  
Send you marketing messages, if you choose to receive them  
If you create an account, we will store your name, address and email, which will be used to populate the checkout for future orders.

We generally store information about you for as long as we need the information for the purposes for which we collect and use it, and we are not legally required to continue to keep it. This includes your name, email address and billing addresses.

We will also store comments or reviews, if you choose to leave them.

We will also store posts and replies on our support forums if you choose to ask for support.

###### Contact Forms

When you submit a contact form on our website the contents of the form, including any personal information, will be sent to our team via email in an effort to support you. We do not use these emails for other marketing but solely to respond to the contents of the form.

###### Reviews and Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

###### Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track behaviour of our website visitors however no personal data is transferred to Google Analytics. For more information see their [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

#### Who on our team has access

Members of our team have access to the information you provide us. For example, Administrators can access:

Order information like what was purchased and when it was purchased, and  
Customer information like your name, email address, and billing information.

Our support team members have access to order history to help support you.

###### What we share with others

We share information with third parties who help us provide our orders and store services to you; for example —

 **Accepting Payments**  
We accept payments through Braintree payments (a PayPal service). When processing payments, some of your data will be passed to PayPal, including information required to process or support the payment, such as the purchase total and billing information.

Please see the Braintree and PayPal Privacy Policy for more details.

 **Other Service Providers**  
We may use third parties to help operate our website, authenticate users and deliver products and services, and may share some of your data with our service providers, vendors, suppliers, and other third parties that provide products or services for our website and services (such as website or database hosting companies, authentication providers, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). Unless otherwise stated, these companies do not have any right to use the data we provide to them beyond what is necessary for them to assist us.

#### Browser Cookies

We use cookies to keep track of cart contents while you’re browsing our site.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish a topic or reply on the forums, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the topic or reply you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Cookies can be used for users that arrive on our site by following an affiliate link from one of our affiliates. These cookies contain no personal or user-specific information and are only randomly generated numbers that match your browser with one of our affiliates.

#### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

An example of this found in many of our articles is YouTube embedded tutorial videos.

#### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. For either request please email [info@kadencethemes.com](mailto:info@kadencethemes.com)

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us by email at [info@kadencethemes.com](mailto:info@kadencethemes.com)
